Women's Rights Collection, 1789-2000 (bulk 1864-1983)
Sophia Smith Collection, Smith College
Women's rights collection
1789-2000
1864-1983
MS 397
51 boxes, 23 volumes (25.75 linear ft.)
Sophia Smith Collection Smith College Northampton, MA
This collection contains both printed materials and original sources documenting the broad spectrum of women's rights struggles and movements from the late eighteenth century to the present, primarily in the United States. Materials include biographical writings on individuals who made significant contributions to women's rights; an important concentration of sources on women's rights conferences and conventions; records pertaining to the E.R.A. fight; records of the President's Commission on the Status of Women and state-level Commissions on the Status of Women; and documents and publications of many national and local women's organizations.
Scope and Contents of the Collection
The Women's Rights Collection contains a large quantity and variety of material including both published and unpublished sources documenting the broad spectrum of women's rights struggles and movements from the late eighteenth century to the present. The vast majority of the material relates to women's rights in the United States from 1846 to 1983.
Organization of the Collection
This collection is organized into eight series:
I. GENERAL
II. BIOGRAPHICAL MATERIALS
III. CONFERENCES
IV. EQUAL RIGHTS AMENDMENT
V. LEGAL STATUS
VI. ORGANIZATIONS
VII. COMMISSIONS ON THE STATUS OF WOMEN
VIII. COUNTRIES
OVERSIZE MATERIALS
ITEMS ON SHELF
Information on Use
Terms of Access and Use
The collection is open to research according to the regulations of the Sophia Smith Collection.
Additions to the Collection
Periodic additions are expected and may not be reflected in this finding aid.
History of the Collection
Materials in this collection were either purchased or given to the Sophia Smith Collection by various donors. Some items were removed from other collections.
Search Terms
Equal rights amendments--United States--History--Sources; Feminists--United States--History--Sources; Women--Developing countries--History--20th century--Sources; Women--Legal status, laws, etc.--History--Sources; Women--Legal status, laws, etc.--History--Sources; Women's rights--Congresses; Women's rights--History-Sources; Women's rights--International cooperation--History--20th century--Sources; International Women's Year, 1975; National Women's Conference (1st: 1977: Houston, Tex.); National Women's Political Caucus--History; United States. Citizens' Advisory Committee on the Status of Women; United States. President's Commission on the Status of Women; Woman's Centennial Congress (1940: New York, N.Y.); Woman's Rights Convention (1st: 1848: Seneca Falls, N.Y.); World Conference of the United Nations Decade for Women: Equality, Development, and Peace (1980: Copenhagen, Denmark); Blackwell, Henry Browne, 1825-1909--Biography--Sources; Bloomer, Amelia Jenks, 1818-1894 --Biography--Sources; Foster, Abigail Kelley, 1810-1887--Biography--Sources; Gilman, Charlotte Perkins, 1860-1935--Biography--Sources; Grimke, Angelina Emily, 1805-1879--Biography--Sources; Grimke, Sarah Moore, 1792-1873--Biography--Sources; Hamilton, Gail, 1833-1896--Biography--Sources; Kenyon, Dorothy, 1888-1972--Biography--Sources; Mott, Lucretia, 1793-1880--Biography--Sources; Paul, Alice, 1885-1977--Biography--Sources; Rose, Ernestine L. (Ernestine Louise), 1810-1892--Biography--Sources; Stanton, Elizabeth Cady, 1815-1902--Biography--Sources; Stone, Lucy, 1818-1893--Biography-Sources; Terrell, Mary Church, 1863-1954; Truth, Sojourner, d. 1883--Biography--Sources; Wells-Barnett, Ida B., 1862-1931--Biography--Sources; Sophia Smith Collection
Additional Information
Related Material
Related material can be found in the papers or records of some of these individuals and organizations in the SSC.
- SERIES I. GENERAL
  SERIES I. GENERAL includes writings and speeches by and about feminists from pamphlets dated as early as 1814, to analytical articles written in the 1970s by well-known women's historians such as Gerda Lerner and William O'Neill.
- SERIES II. BIOGRAPHICAL MATERIALS
  SERIES II. BIOGRAPHICAL MATERIALS includes material relating to significant figures who supported and agitated for women's rights, particularly those who made major contributions to the nineteenth century woman's rights movement, but also more recent feminist activists. Individuals represented include Ida Wells Barnett, Henry Brown Blackwell, Amelia Jenks Bloomer, Abigail Kelley Foster, Charlotte Perkins Gilman, Sarah and Angelina Grimke, Marietta Holley, Dorothy Kenyon, Lucretia Coffin Mott, Alice Paul, Ernestine Rose, Sojourner Truth, Elizabeth Cady Stanton, Lucy Stone, and Mary Church Terrell. Types of material include articles, memorials, newspaper clippings, pamphlets, and photographs, books, and a small amount of correspondence.
- SERIES III. CONFERENCES
  SERIES III. CONFERENCES includes an important concentration of published sources documenting women's rights conferences and conventions. Types of material include, correspondence, minutes, newspaper clippings, photographs, planning material, publicity, published proceedings, reports, resolutions, and memorabilia. Under the International Women's Year conference (1977), there are audio recordings of speeches and sessions. Others documented include the Seneca Falls Convention of 1848; the Women's Centennial Congress in New York City, 1940; the Conference on the Role of Women at Smith College in 1947; the Seneca Falls Centennial Convention of 1948; International Women's Year State Conferences held in 1977; International Women's Year Conference in Houston, 1977; and the United Nations Decade for Women World Conference in Copenhagen, 1980. There are also records pertaining to lesser-known nineteenth century woman's rights local conventions in Akron, Ohio, 1851; West Chester, Pennsylvania, 1852; Cleveland, Ohio, 1854; New York City, 1856; Boston, 1859; the New York Church of the Puritans in 1866; and the American Equal Rights Association Convention in New York in 1867, among others.
- SERIES IV. EQUAL RIGHTS AMENDMENT
  The long history of struggles related to efforts to pass and ratify the ERA from 1920 to 1983 is well documented in Series IV. EQUAL RIGHTS AMENDMENT with articles, bibliographies, correspondence, legislation, lists, memorabilia, memoranda, newspaper clippings, pamphlets, and publicity contained in the collection. There are interviews with feminist activists that were conducted for a 1983 project entitled The Fight for E.R.A.: Leaders, Strategies, and Directions, by Jennifer Jackman and Tamar Raphael. The 28 interviewees include Ruth Adams, Carol Atkins, Kathy Bonk, Pat and Twiss Butler, Susan Catania, Lillian Ciarrochi, Alice Cohan, Mary Jean Collins, Mary Crisp, Diane Cutri, Betsy Dunn, Catherine East, Don Edwards, Vicki Ferguson, Pat Frank, Audrey Ghizzoni, Sheila Greenwald, Mariwyn Heath, Mildred Jeffrey, Beth Leopold, Ann Lewis, Colette Roberts, Reed Gloria Sackman, Eleanor Smeal, Jane Wells-Schooley, Jinx Wingard, and Molly Yard. There are interview notes, and photographs, as well as audio recordings for some, not all, interviews.
- SERIES V. LEGAL STATUS
  SERIES V. LEGAL STATUS documents changes in women's legal status in individual states and in the United States at-large.
- SERIES VI. ORGANIZATIONS
  SERIES VI. ORGANIZATIONS contains materials generated by women's political and equal rights groups such as the Equity Network, Human Rights for Women, International Alliance of Women, the National Advisory Committee for Women, the National Women's Education Fund, and the Massachusetts Women's Political Caucus and the National Women's Political Caucus.
- SERIES VII. COMMISSIONS ON THE STATUS OF WOMEN
  SERIES VII. includes Records generated by the President's Commission on the Status of Women (circa 1960s-70s) and the various state level Commissions on the Status of Women are also a significant part of the collection. Included in this section are published articles, briefs, pamphlets, publicity, reports, meeting agendas, minutes, and correspondence.
  [Note: this section is unprocessed and contains many duplicated materials]
- SERIES VIII. COUNTRIES
  SERIES VIII. COUNTRIES includes a small amount of material relating to women's rights in countries outside the United States: Africa, Albania, Asia, Australia, Canada, China, England, France, Germany, Israel, Italy, Japan, Lebanon, Mexico, Norway, Pakistan, Philippines, Portugal, San Marino, Spain, Thailand, Turkey, and Vietnam. International materials can also be found in the files relating to the International Women's Year conferences in Houston, Texas and Copenhagen under CONFERENCES.
- SERIES I. GENERAL
  - Pamphlets, [see also photocopies on shelf]
    - 1846-58 (Box 1, Folder 1)
    - Women's Rights: tracts 1-6, 1851 (Box 1, Folder 2)
    - 1867-1977 (Box 1, Folder 3-4)
    - Women's Rights Pamphlets, Cornell University Collection (microfiche)1814-1912, [loose on shelf] (Box 1)
    - The Sisterhood: pamphlet, circa 1870 (Box 1, Folder 5)
  - Speeches
    - George William Curtis: speeches and clippings1867 (Box 1, Folder 6)
    - Great American Women's Speeches: cassette tapes1973 (Box 1)
  - Writings
    - Savery, Annie, Rev. T.O. Rice on the Subordination of Women: clippings1871 (Box 1, Folder 7)
    - Petition to Improve the Condition of Married Womenn.d. (Box 1, Folder 8)
    - A Reply to John Stuart Mill on the Subjection of Women (Philadelphia)1870 (Box 1)
    - Articles
      - Leland, Marine
        - Radio talks over CBC: transcripts1955-56 (Box 2, Folder 1)
        - Speech at Business & Professional Women, Northampton1950 (Box 2, Folder 2)
      - Lerner, Gerda, Women's Rights and American Feminismn.d. (Box 2, Folder 3)
      - Virginia Slims American Women's Opinion Poll1972 (Box 2, Folder 4)
      - O'Neill, William L., Feminism as a Radical Ideology1968 (Box 2, Folder 5)
      - Powell, Rose Arnold: writings1933 (Box 2, Folder 6)
      - Shegda, Paula, Do Women Advertise Themselves Enough?: The Split in the Feminist Movement1869-1890 (1975) (Box 2, Folder 7)
      - Miscellaneous articles on the status of women1963-65 (Box 2, Folder 8)
    - Publications: NWHP Gazelle: "Living the Legacy," 1998 (Box 2, Folder 8a)
  - The Women's Charter: What and Why?: articles, correspondence, and press releases1936-38 (Box 2, Folder 9)
  - Essays from "TABS: Aids for Ending Sexism in SchoolsSpr 1978 (Box 2, Folder 10)
  - "Side-by-Side" (re-enactments of scenes from women's history)1848-1920 (phonograph record) (Box 2)
    [see OVERSIZE MATERIALS]
- SERIES II. BIOGRAPHICAL MATERIALS
  - Barnett, Ida Wells: photograph and clippings1931 (Box 3, Folder 1)
  - Blackwell, Henry Brown: photographs, pamphlet, and manuscript1910-27 (Box 3, Folder 2)
  - Bloomer, Amelia Jenks: article and mailing (with mini bloomers attached)1939-48 (Box 3, Folder 3)
  - Cooley, Winifred Harper: short biographies and article1915-2002 (Box 3, Folder 4)
    [see also Oversize Materials]
  - Dodge, Mary Abigail (Gail Hamilton): pamphlets and article, circa 1840-96 (Box 3, Folder 5)
  - Foster, Abigail Kelley: pamphlet and biography1965-84 (Box 3, Folder 6)
  - Gaston, Lucy Page: article1924 (Box 3, Folder 7)
  - Gilman, Charlotte Perkins: articles, photographs, pamphlets, correspondence, and thesis1905-80 (Box 3, Folder 8-10)
  - Grimke, Sarah (1792-1873) and Angelina (1805-1879): pamphlet, 1970 (Box 3, Folder 11)
  - Holley, Marietta (Box 3)
    [see Books on shelf]
  - Kenyon, Dorothy: information about ERA1971 (Box 3, Folder 12)
  - Mott, Lucretia Coffin: speeches, articles, pamphlets, and photographs1849-1959 (Box 3, Folder 13-14)
  - Paul, Alice: photographs and articles1917-77 (Box 3, Folder 15)
  - Robb, Lynda Bird Johnson: clippings1979 (Box 3, Folder 16)
  - Rose, Ernestine Louise Potowski: address and clippings1948-49 (Box 3, Folder 17)
  - Sojourner Truth: photographs, pamphlets, Narrative of Sojourner Truth, a Northern Slave, and biography1850-1983 (Box 3, Folder 18-19)
  - Stanton, Elizabeth Cady: pamphlets, newsletters, clippings, correspondence, photographs, and speeches1827-1972 (Box 4, Folder 1-5)
  - Stone, Lucy: book, photographs, correspondence, and speeches1846-1978 (Box 4, Folder 6-8)
    [see also OVERSIZE MATERIALS]
  - Terrell, Mary Church: clippings and program1951-54 (Box 4, Folder 9)
- SERIES III. CONFERENCES
  - "Role of Women," Smith College1947
    - Scrapbook (Box 5)
    - Miscellaneous items (Box 5, Folder 1)
    - Minutes: Volumes I and II (Box 5)
    - General: programs, clippings, SCAN, press releases, and correspondence1947 (Box 5, Folder 2-4)
    - Correspondence1946-47 (Box 5, Folder 5-6)
    - Speeches1947 (Box 5, Folder 7-8)
    - Photographs1947 (Box 5, Folder 9)
    - "Woman's Rights and Other 'Reforms' in Seneca Falls," 1965 (Box 5, Folder 10)
  - World Conference of the International Women's Year, Mexico City, 1975
    - General, 1975 (Box 5A, Folder 1)
    - Agenda items 9 and 10, 1975 (Box 5A, Folder 2)
    - World Plan of Action, 1975 (Box 5A, Folder 3)
    - Background papers, 1975 (Box 5A, Folder 4)
  - National Commission on the Observance of International Women's Year - State Conferences, 1977
    - Alabama: correspondence, report, program, and clippings1977 (Box 6, Folder 1)
    - Alaska: evaluations and report1977 (Box 6, Folder 2)
    - American Samoa: pamphlet and report1977 (Box 6, Folder 3)
    - Arizona: final report1977 (Box 6, Folder 4)
    - Arkansas: conference information and 'litter and locator bag,' 1977 (Box 6, Folder 5)
    - California: pamphlet, final report, and questionnaires1977 (Box 7, Folder 1)
    - Colorado: plan of action1977 (Box 7, Folder 2)
    - Connecticut: report and clippings1977 (Box 7, Folder 3)
    - Delaware: final report1977 (Box 7, Folder 4)
    - Florida: binder1977 (Box 7, Folder 5)
    - Georgia: report1977 (Box 7, Folder 6)
    - Guam: final report1977 (Box 7, Folder 7)
    - Hawaii: pamphlet1979 (Box 7, Folder 8)
    - Idaho: recommendations and final report1977 (Box 7, Folder 9)
    - Illinois: book1977 (Box 8, Folder 1)
    - Indiana: petition, recommendations, and reports1977 (Box 8, Folder 2)
    - Iowa: final report1977 (Box 8, Folder 3)
    - Kansas: report, voter information and program1977 (Box 8, Folder 4)
    - Kentucky
      - "Voices of Kentucky Women": report1977 (Box 8)
      - Observance of International Women's Year: Appendix1977 (Box 8)
    - Louisiana: correspondence, recommendations, and book1977 (Box 9, Folder 1)
    - Maine: report1977 (Box 9, Folder 2)
    - Maryland: proclamation and pamphlet1977 (Box 9, Folder 3)
    - Massachusetts: Women at Home in the World (report)1977 (Box 10)
    - Michigan: report1977 (Box 10)
    - Minnesota: report and agenda1977 (Box 10, Folder 1)
    - Mississippi: report1977 (Box 10)
    - Missouri: reports1977 (Box 10, Folder 2)
    - Montana: vote results and final report1977 (Box 11, Folder 1)
    - Nevada: pamphlet and final report1977 (Box 11, Folder 2)
    - New Hampshire: plan for action and final reports1977 (Box 11, Folder 3)
    - New Jersey: report1977 (Box 11)
    - New Mexico: final report1977 (Box 12, Folder 1)
    - New York
      - Transcripts1977 (Box 12)
      - Correspondence, ballot questions, and first meeting1974-77 (Box 13, Folder 1)
      - Report (Box 13)
        [see Oversize Materials]
    - North Carolina: report1977 (Box 13, Folder 2)
    - North Dakota: final report1977 (Box 13)
    - Ohio: book1977 (Box 13, Folder 3)
    - Oklahoma: correspondence, workshop results, and final report1977 (Box 14, Folder 1-2)
    - Oregon: final report1977 (Box 14, Folder 3)
    - Pennsylvania: "Womankind," 1977 (Box 14)
    - Puerto Rico: documents and final report1977 (Box 14, Folder 4)
      [See also Added materials, box 51]
    - Rhode Island: report1977 (Box 15)
    - South Carolina: final report and resolutions1977 (Box 15, Folder 1)
    - South Dakota: report1977 (Box 15, Folder 2)
    - Tennessee: ballot, pamphlets, photographs, minutes, and recommendations1977 (Box 15, Folder 3)
    - Texas: final report and flyer1977 (Box 15, Folder 4)
    - Utah: final report1977 (Box 16, Folder 1)
    - Vermont: final report1977 (Box 16, Folder 2)
    - Virgin Islands: survey and report1977 (Box 16, Folder 3)
    - Virginia: final report, conference information, and clippings1977 (Box 16, Folder 4)
    - Washington, D.C.: minutes and plan of action1977 (Box 17, Folder 1)
    - Washington (state): policy statements and final report1977 (Box 17, Folder 2)
    - West Virginia: resolutions, report, and recommendations1977 (Box 17, Folder 3)
    - Wisconsin: draft of report and supporting material1977 (Box 17, Folder 4)
    - Wyoming: report1977 (Box 17, Folder 5)
  - IWY National Women's Conference (Houston), November 1977
    [see also cassette tapes on shelf]
    - Daily Breakthrough and bulletins1977 (Box 18, Folder 1)
    - Official Briefing Book (Box 18)
    - Memorabilia: calendar, t-shirt, flyer, and song lyrics1977 (Box 18, Folder 2)
    - Articles, clippings, speeches: clippings, magazines, script, flyers, and press release1977 (Box 18, Folder 3)
    - Clippings and magazine1977 (Box 18, Folder 4)
    - Pamphlets, magazine, bulletin, resolutions, and newspaper1977 (Box 18, Folder 5)
    - Resolutions and news1977 (Box 18, Folder 6)
    - Declaration of American women: cassette tape and slides1977 (Box 18, Folder 7)
    - IWY conventions- states: newspaper, manual, pamphlet, and clipping1976-77 (Box 18, Folder 8)
    - Exhibit material: letter cut-outs and magazine pages1977, [see also Oversize Materials] (Box 18, Folder 9)
    - "Decade of Achievement": report1977 (Box 18, Folder 10)
  - Pamphlets1978 (Box 18, Folder 11)
  - Mary Rothchild
    - Correspondence1977 (Box 18a, Folder 1)
    - Conference materials1977 (Box 18a, Folder 2)
  - Newspaper clippings1977 (Box 18a, Folder 3)
  - Reports1977 (Box 18a, Folder 4)
  - Laws, executive orders, and resolutions1977 (Box 18a, Folder 5)
  - Educational Equality1977 (Box 18a, Folder 6)
  - ERA and Civil Rights1977 (Box 18a, Folder 7)
  - Gay Rights1977 (Box 18a, Folder 8)
  - Housing1977 (Box 18a, Folder 9)
  - Labor1977 (Box 18a, Folder 10)
  - Memorabilia1977 (Box 18a, Folder 11)
  - Miscellaneous
    - Pamphlets1977 (Box 18a, Folder 12)
    - Publications1977 (Box 18a, Folder 13)
  - UN World Conference, Decade for Women, Copenhagen1980
    - Index to microfiche (Box 19, Folder 1)
    - Microfiche (Box 19, Folder 2)
    - Background Press Release; Secretary General's Opening Remarks (Box 19)
    - List of Participants (Box 19)
    - Overview of Progress/Obstacles at the National Level (Box 19)
    - World Plan of Action
      - Employment review/evaluation (Box 19)
      - Health review/evaluation (Box 19)
      - Education review/education (Box 19)
      - National machinery review/evaluation (Box 19)
    - Descriptive list of National Machineries (Box 19)
    - Political Participation, International Co-op and International Peace: review (Box 19)
    - Women in Rural Areas: statistical abstract (Box 19)
    - Technological Change and Microelectronics for Women Workers (Box 19)
    - Information/communication as developed resources; employment effects of science and technology (Box 19)
    - International Seminar -- Women and Media (Box 19)
    - Influence/Mass Media/Attitudes toward Societal Roles of Men and Women (Box 19)
    - Health Effects/Cultural Practices on Women and Children (Box 19)
    - Women's Status/Role in Education and in Economy/Social Areas (Box 19)
    - Reviews/Evaluation of Regional/ Global UN Programmes (Box 19)
    - UN Conference Recommendations re: Women (Box 19)
    - UN System Agencies re: Decade goals: review (Box 19)
    - ESCAP Regional Preparatory Meeting at New Delhi; Lusaka; Damascus (Box 19)
    - Economic Role of Women in ECE Region (Box 19)
    - UN Dept. of International Economic and Social Affairs re: World Plan of Action: review (Box 19)
    - Decade for Women Voluntary Fund: Secretary General's report (Box 19)
    - Dept. Technology Co-op for Development: report (Box 19)
    - Industrial Development Organization: report (Box 19)
    - Women, children, and development: UNICEF report (Box 19)
    - World Food Programme and Decade for Women (Box 19)
    - Ongoing and Future Programs re: Decade for Women: UNITAR report (Box 19)
    - Measures Taken to Implement UN Decade for Women: ILO report (Box 19)
    - Integration of Women in Rural Development: FAO report (Box 19)
    - School Education for Girls: UNESCO report (Box 19)
    - Health and Status of Women: WHO report (Box 19)
    - "Invisible" Women in Development: World Bank report (Box 19)
    - Rural Women's Participation in Development: UNDP report (Box 19)
    - Policies/Programs in the Field of Women/Population/Development: UNFPA report (Box 19)
    - Conference of Non-Aligned/Other Developing Countries on Role of Women in Development (Box 19)
    - Convention on the Elimination of All Forms of Discrimination against Women (Box 19)
    - Preparatory Committee Report (Sessions 1-3) (Box 19)
    - Commission on the Status of Women Report (Sessions 27-28) (Box 19)
    - Effective Mobilization/Integration of Women in Development (Box 19)
    - Situation of Women Refugees Worldwide (Box 19)
    - Women's Role in Liberation Struggles in Zimbabwe, Namibia, and South Africa (Box 19)
    - Assistance Measures for Women in Southern Africa (Box 19)
    - Apartheid Effects of Women's Status in South Africa and Namibia (Box 19)
    - Lusaka Declaration on Racism/Racial Prejudice (Box 19)
    - Apartheid and Women's Employment/Women in Trade Unions (Box 19)
    - Women and Apartheid: reports of Montreal and Helsinki Seminars (Box 19)
    - Israeli Occupation Effects on Palestinian Women: Assistance Measures to Palestinian Women (Box 19)
    - Social/Economic Conditions of Palestinian Women (Box 19)
    - National Reports
      - Israel (Box 19)
      - Japan (Box 19)
      - Canada (Box 19)
      - India (Box 19)
      - Poland (Box 19)
      - Austria (Box 19)
      - Byelorussia (Box 19)
      - USA (Box 19)
      - China (PR) (Box 19)
      - New Zealand (Box 19)
      - Round-up press release (Box 19)
    - Summary
      - Contents and abbreviations (Box 19)
      - Background; National, International and Regional Levels of Action (Box 19)
      - Resolutions and Origins of the Conference (Box 19)
      - Organization of Work; General Debate; Report of First Committee (Box 19)
      - Reports of Second and Third Committees; adoption of conference report, Corrigendum (Box 19)
    - Program of Action: information paper (Box 19)
    - Resolutions: information paper (Box 19)
    - Women 1980: DESI newsletters (1-8) (Box 19)
  - Conventions
    - Women's Centennial Congress, NYC (1940): clipping, minutes, programs, correspondence, pamphlets, book, and newsletters1939-40 (Box 20, Folder 1)
    - Seneca Falls Convention (1848) (Box 20)
      - Report, photograph, honor roll, and pamphlets1848 (Box 20, Folder 2)
      - Centennial (1948)
        - Volume of papers1948 (Box 20, Folder 3)
        - Clippings and newspaper1948 (Box 20, Folder 4)
        - Pageant scripts (English and Spanish) and news reports1940-48 (Box 20, Folder 5)
        - Seneca Falls Historical Society: pamphlet1972 (Box 20, Folder 6)
        - Memorabilia: pamphlets, napkin, envelopes, map, and magazines1937-48 (Box 20, Folder 7)
    - Akron, OH: book1973 (reprint of 1851 proceedings) (Box 20, Folder 8)
    - West Chester, PA: proceedings1852 (Box 20, Folder 9)
    - Cleveland, OH: circular1854 (Box 20, Folder 10)
    - Broadway Tabernacle, NYC: pamphlet1856 (Box 20, Folder 11)
    - Mercantile Hall, Boston: reports1859 (Box 20, Folder 12)
    - Church of the Puritans, NYC: proceedings1866 (Box 20, Folder 13)